{
  "0": [
	"Wonderkins",
	"Athletics",
	"Awesomeness",
	"Potpourri",
	"O'Brien",
	"Family Facts"
  ],
  "200": [
	{
	  "category": 1,
	  "question": "Accepted into a study abroad in Galway Ireland",
	  "answer": "Bridgette O'Brien Robertson",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 2,
	  "question": "Finished his first 5K race",
	  "answer": "Myles Kim O'Brien Robertson",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 3,
	  "question": "The cutest little day late leprechaun",
	  "answer": "William Parker",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 4,
	  "question": "Is a West Port surfer dude, Stevens Pass snowboarding rock star and wheeler and dealer on the world wide web, building computers and bartering for goods",
	  "answer": "Michael O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 5,
	  "question": "Need Question",
	  "answer": "John O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 6,
	  "question": "The year O'Briens came over from Ireland",
	  "answer": "1880",
	  "show": true
	}
  ],
  "400": [
	{
	  "category": 1,
	  "question": "Made a 4.0 GPA as a Freshman at O'Dea Highschool",
	  "answer": "Rudy Thatcher",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 2,
	  "question": "Became the setter on her National Volleyball team",
	  "answer": "Aubrey Jones",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 3,
	  "question": "Honored by the Stanwood Camano Island Chamber of Commerce as woman of the year for her contributions to the community. And Awarded the Stanwood/Camano Island Spirit of Philanthropy Award â€“ Pay It Forward because of her spirit of giving time to her community",
	  "answer": "Jill Vail",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 4,
	  "question": "Married on September 30th, 2017",
	  "answer": "Devon Jones and Lauren Kopp",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 5,
	  "question": "Known to be keenly passionate about his politics and support of working people. People may not know that he read 3-5 newspapers every day and was deeply engaged in current events. Before the cable news environment, when people listened to Larry King on the radio, he was so knowledgeable that he became a 'caller' who Larry regular spoke with on his show. Larry would say, '_____ in Seattle...what do you think?'",
	  "answer": "Jerry O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 6,
	  "question": "The team that Seattle University, led by John and Ed O'Brien, beat in 1952",
	  "answer": "Harlem Globetrotters",
	  "show": true
	}
  ],
  "600": [
	{
	  "category": 1,
	  "question": "An (almost) being a graduate of the University of Washington with a degree in public health",
	  "answer": "Megan De La Riva",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 2,
	  "question": "Turned an extra point poor snap into a perfect pass for a 2 point conversion",
	  "answer": "Matthew Mounsey",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 3,
	  "question": "An all star running back, averaging over 2 touchdowns and 150 yards per game -he led his team to the playoffs where, unfortunately, he tore his ACL and Meniscus - he's on the road to recovery for next year",
	  "answer": "Johnny O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 4,
	  "question": "Put up with Megan for an entire year",
	  "answer": "Drew Burns",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 5,
	  "question": "Went through 3 states and 3 countries in Jim O'Brien Sr's camper",
	  "answer": "Ed O'Brien Family",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 6,
	  "question": "The only O'Brien who served in the military in the last 5 years",
	  "answer": "Eric O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	}
  ],
  "800": [
	{
	  "category": 1,
	  "question": "Became first chair French Horn in Concert Band and First Trumpet in Jazz Band",
	  "answer": "James-Ray McCrumb",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 2,
	  "question": "Chosen for high school team captain of the varsity soccer team as a sophomore while taking all AP classes and maintaining an outstanding GPA",
	  "answer": "Clayre Robinson",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 3,
	  "question": "Drove from New York to Portland to join us at the Party tonight",
	  "answer": "Carla O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 4,
	  "question": "Was promoted to Store Manager of Starbucks",
	  "answer": "Dylan Martorano",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 5,
	  "question": "He was the coach of a semi pro baseball team where a number of his players got promoted to the minor leagues",
	  "answer": "Bill O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 6,
	  "question": "Michael O'Brien started this business when first arriving to New Jersey from Ireland in 1880",
	  "answer": "A bakery",
	  "show": true
	}
  ],
  "1000": [
	{
	  "category": 1,
	  "question": "Earned a 3.6 GPA and made varsity soccer her first year of High School",
	  "answer": "Elle O'Brien",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 2,
	  "question": "Accepted at Seattle University and received the Belarmine Academic Scholarship and will be a walk on for the SU Basketball Team in the Fall",
	  "answer": "Matthew Vail",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 3,
	  "question": "Named Boy of the Year at his High School",
	  "answer": "Cody Vail",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 4,
	  "question": "Took on the challenge of beginning French while continuing her study of German",
	  "answer": "Imogene McCrumb",
	  "show": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 5,
	  "question": "The Best Guy in Town",
	  "answer": "Jim O'Brien",
	  "show": true,
	  "isGpa": true
	},
	{
	  "category": 6,
	  "question": "The associate head coach for the Washington State University track team",
	  "answer": "Julie Taylor",
	  "show": true
	}
  ]
}